Guide to the Bill Andrews Editorial Cartoons and Papers GRAPHICS.038
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bill Andrews Editorial Cartoons and Papers
1941-2011
1968-1977
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Andrews, Bill, 1937-
GRAPHICS.038
41.5 Linear Feet in 11 record cartons, 30 oversize flat boxes, 1 manuscript box, and 56 flat-file folders.
Bill Andrews, born William Grant Andrews on June 2, 1937 in Tucson, Arizona, is a graphic artist, photographer and journalist. After graduating from high school in 1955, he worked as a copy editor, writer, photographer and staff cartoonist at the Arizona Republic in Phoenix, and then as a a one-man art department at KNME-TV in Albuquerque. In April 1963, shortly after graduating from the University of New Mexico, Andrews moved to New York City, where, he began to draw cartoons for the La Nueva Voz. Shortly thereafter, he was hired as a staff photographer for The Daily World, and later became a staff cartoonist. He created artwork for the paper on a daily basis, and also authored comic strips, articles and music reviews. After leaving the paper in October 1977, Andrews returned to Arizona, where he worked in Arizona State University's Graphics Department from January 1978 until 1997. The collection contains artwork created by Bill Andrews throughout his life, including drawings, prints and paintings, as well as materials gathered or created in preparation of this artwork such as idea files, clippings and notes. The large majority of the material in the collection dates from the period that Andrews was employed by the Daily World in New York City. Cartoons from this period deal with a variety of political and social issues, including the Presidential administration of Richard Nixon, the Vietnam War, housing conditions and United States-Soviet Union relations. Material from before and after Andrews' tenure at the paper is also present in the collection, including his employment at the Arizona Republic, KNME-TV, the University of New Mexico and Arizona State University.
Separated Materials
Artwork created by other artists for publication in the Daily Worker, The Worker and the Daily World including Fred Ellis, Ollie Harrington and Erik (James Erickson) was separated to the Daily Worker/Daily World Cartoons Collection (GRAPHICS 24.001). Negatives were separated to The Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS 223.001, and photographs were separated to The Daily Worker and the Daily World Photographs Collection (PHOTOS 223).
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in six series: I: Preparatory Material; II: Finished Artwork; III: Pre Press Prints; IV: Subject Files; V: Ephemera, and VI: Artwork by Others. Series II: Finished Artwork and Series III: Pre Press Prints both contain subseries for Andrews' comic strips.
All series are arranged first alphabetically and then chronologically. Due to space constraints, physical arrangement of materials does not match intellectual arrangement.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains artwork created by Bill Andrews throughout his life, including drawings, prints and paintings, as well as materials gathered or created in preparation of this artwork such as idea files, clippings and notes. Halftoned and sized Pre Press Prints of his artwork, many of which have spot corrections to highlights, are also present in the collection. Also included are Subject Files containing Andrews' correspondence, published artwork, clippings of other artists' work, leaflets, and files related to organizations of which he was a member. A small number of ephemeral and three-dimensional objects are also part of the collection, as is a small amount of artwork given to Andrews by other artists.
The large majority of the material in the collection dates from the period that Andrews was employed by the Daily World in New York City. Cartoons from this period deal with a variety of political and social issues, including the Presidential administration of Richard Nixon, the Vietnam War, housing conditions and United States-Soviet Union relations. Generally speaking, these cartoons reflecting the editorial perspective of the Daily World as well as the Communist Party of the United States of America.
Material from before and after Andrews' tenure at the Daily World is also present in the collection. This includes promotional artwork from the Arizona Republic, KNME-TV and the University of New Mexico. A significant amount of material, including promotional material, departmental brochures, informational flyers and event posters, produced while Andrews was employed by Arizona State University is also part of the collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Bill Andrews, 2009. The accession number associated with this collection is 2011.120.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Biographical Note
Bill Andrews, born William Grant Andrews on June 2, 1937 in Tucson, Arizona, is a graphic artist, photographer and journalist.
Raised in a working class family, Andrews began drawing at an early age, copying popular comic strip characters and inventing his own while still in middle school. After graduating from high school in 1955, he worked as a copy editor, writer, photographer and staff cartoonist at the Arizona Republic in Phoenix. During this time, he became politically radicalized through an acquaintance (and Communist Party member) named Joe Owen with whom he traded recordings of early jazz and blues musicians. In 1959, he moved to Albuquerque, New Mexico, and enrolled in the University of New Mexico, where he majored in Art Education and minored in Government. He graduated with honors in 1963 with a Bachelor of Fine Arts Degree. While attending classes, he worked as a one-man art department at KNME-TV in Albuquerque.
In April 1963, shortly after graduating from the University of New Mexico, Andrews moved to New York City to become a graphic artist. He found short-term employment as a commercial artist, as well as a cartoonist for La Nueva Voz. After being introduced to staff at The Worker through his contacts at New World Review in 1964, he began to draw cartoons for the paper. When The Worker changed its name to The Daily World and began daily publication in 1968, he was hired as a staff photographer. He worked for the paper and its associated Spanish-language papers El Mundo Diario and Voz del Pueblo until October 1977. Although initially hired as a photographer, Andrews soon became a staff cartoonist as well, creating artwork for the paper on a daily basis, as well as authoring comic strips including "Is This the Way it Was?," "Nix!" and "The Optic Nerve." In addition, he wrote articles and music reviews for the paper, sometimes under the pseudonyms of Stark Jeffreys and Neil Harris. During this time, he received the Newspaper Guild of New York's Page One Award honoring outstanding achievement in journalism for his cartoons in 1972, 1973 and 1974. He was also awarded a Silurian Society Medallion in 1974.
After leaving the paper in October 1977, Andrews returned to Arizona, where he worked in Arizona State University's Graphics Department from January 1978 until 1997.
William Grant Andrews passed away at home in Lake Montezuma, Arizona on May 20, 2013 at age 76.
Related Archival Materials
Daily Worker/Daily World Photographs Collection (PHOTOS 223)
Daily Worker/Daily World Negatives Collection (PHOTOS 223.1)
Daily Worker/Daily World Cartoons Collection (GRAPHICS 24.1)
Communist Party of the United States of America Oral History Collection (OH 065)
New York (N.Y.) |x Social conditions |y 20th century.; Photographs.; Political cartoons.; Political cartoons -- United States.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Printed ephemera.; Daily world (New York, N.Y.); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Arizona State University; Communist Party of the United States of America; Andrews, Bill, 1937-
- Series I: Preparatory Material
  Scope and Content Note
  Contains material gathered or created by Andrews in preparation for creating cartoons or other artwork. This includes clippings of newspapers (often annotated by Andrews), his notes on news items and sketches in pencil. Also included are idea files, which contain a combination of clippings, notes and sketches on particular themes or topics. A small number of sketchbooks and two rolls of sketches are also part of this series.
  Most of the material in this series was collected or created while Andrews was employed by the Daily World. As a result, many of the clippings, sketches and notes respond to current events, including the Vietnam War, the Attica Prison riots, and the activities of President Richard M. Nixon, including his resignation.
  A small amount of material was also created by Andrews when he worked for Arizona State University. These sketches are for promotional brochures, fliers and posters.
  - Clippings, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Numbered Idea Files and Index, undated (Box 1, Folder 14-66, Box 2, Folder 67-94)
    Contains a set of numbered folders holding sketches. Researchers will need to consult Andrews' alphabetical index to these files (located in Box 1, Folder 14) in order to find sketches for a particular subject. Sketches related to a given topic may be located in more than one file, and any given file contains sketches pertaining to multiple topics.
  - Idea Files: Acceptable Ideas (I), undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Idea Files: Acceptable Ideas (II), undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Idea Files: Acceptable Ideas (II), undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Idea Files: Cartoon Theme Notes, 1974-1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Idea Files: Daily World Promotion, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Idea Files: Forgotten Americans Series, 1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Idea Files: Fresh Themes, 1971-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Idea Files: The Optic Nerve, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Idea Files: World at Weakend, 1974-1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Notes, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Notes, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Notes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Notes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Notes, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Notes, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Notes, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Sketches, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Sketches, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 392)
  - Sketches, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Sketches, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 393)
  - Sketches, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Sketches, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Sketches, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Sketches, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Sketches, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Sketches, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Sketches, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Sketches, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Sketches, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Sketches, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Sketches, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Sketches, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Sketches, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Sketches, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Sketches, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Sketches, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Sketches, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Sketches, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Sketches, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Sketches, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Sketches, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Sketches, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Sketches, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Sketches, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Sketches, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Sketches, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Sketches, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Sketches, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Sketches, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 197A)
  - Sketches, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Sketches, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Sketches, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Sketches, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Sketches, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 255)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 31, Folder 394)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 31, Folder 395)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 31, Folder 396)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 31, Folder 397)
  - Sketches: Arizona State University, undated (Box 31, Folder 398)
  - Sketchbooks, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Sketch Rolls, undated (Box 37)
- Series II: Finished Artwork
  Contains the final versions of Andrews' artwork before it was screened and sized for publication. Most of this artwork consists of single frame pen and ink cartoons, and much of it is oversize.
  Most of the material in this series was created while Andrews was employed by the Daily World. As a result, this artwork is largely editorial in nature, responding to current events from the perspective of the Daily World and the Communist Party of the United States of America.
  A small amount of material was also created by Andrews when he worked for Arizona State University. This artwork consists of promotional brochures, fliers and posters for the University as a whole as well as specific departments or offices.
  - Finished Artwork, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1963 (Box 24, Folder 328)
  - Finished Artwork, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 260)
  - Finished Artwork, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 289)
  - Finished Artwork, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Finished Artwork, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Finished Artwork, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Finished Artwork, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 261)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1965 - May 1965 (Box 14, Folder 262)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1965 - Dec 1965 (Box 14, Folder 263)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 329)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Finished Artwork, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1966 - Jun 1966 (Box 14, Folder 264)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1966 - Dec 1966 (Box 15, Folder 265)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Finished Artwork, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 330)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 25, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1967 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Finished Artwork, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 227)
  - Finished Artwork, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 266)
  - Finished Artwork, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Finished Artwork, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 331)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1968 - Jun 1968 (Box 15, Folder 267)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1968 - Dec 1968 (Box 15, Folder 268)
  - Finished Artwork, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Finished Artwork, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Finished Artwork, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Finished Artwork, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1969 - Jun 1969 (Box 15, Folder 269)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1969 - Jun 1969 (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1969 - Dec 1969 (Box 16, Folder 270)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1969 - Dec 1969 (Box 19, Folder 295)
  - Finished Artwork, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Finished Artwork, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Finished Artwork, 1969 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 7)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1970 - Jun 1970 (Box 16, Folder 271)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1970 - Dec 1970 (Box 16, Folder 272)
  - Finished Artwork, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Finished Artwork, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Finished Artwork, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 296)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1971 - Mar 1971 (Box 16, Folder 273)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1971 - Jun 1971 (Box 16, Folder 274)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1971 - Sep 1971 (Box 17, Folder 275)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1971 - Dec 1971 (Box 17, Folder 276)
  - Finished Artwork, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Finished Artwork, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 297)
  - Finished Artwork, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1972 - Mar 1972 (Box 17, Folder 277)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1972 - Apr 1972 (Box 24, Folder 335)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 20, Folder 298)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1972 - Jun 1972 (Box 17, Folder 278)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1972 - Aug 1972 (Box 24, Folder 336)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1972 - Sep 1972 (Box 17, Folder 279)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 20, Folder 299)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 13, 1972 (Box Shared Tamiment 148, Folder 9)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1972 - Dec 1972 (Box 18, Folder 280)
  - Finished Artwork, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 234)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1973 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1973 - Sep 1973 (Flat-file-folder 7 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1973 (Box 25, Folder 339)
  - Finished Artwork, Mar 1973 (Box 25, Folder 340)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1973 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1973 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1973 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1973 (Box 25, Folder 344)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1973 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1973 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1973 (Box 26, Folder 347)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1973 (Box 26, Folder 348)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 1973 (Box 26, Folder 349)
  - Finished Artwork, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 235)
  - Finished Artwork, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 281)
  - Finished Artwork, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - Finished Artwork, 1973 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1974 - Mar 1974 (Box 26, Folder 350)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1974 - Mar 1974 (Flat-file-folder 8 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1974 - Jun 1974 (Box 26, Folder 351)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1974 - Jul 1974 (Flat-file-folder 9 Right, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1974 - Sep 1974 (Box 27, Folder 352)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1974 - Sep 1974 (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1974 (Flat-file-folder 11 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1974 (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1974 - Dec 1974 (Box 27, Folder 353)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 1974 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 237)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 238)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 239)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 240)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 241)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 282)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 301)
  - Finished Artwork, 1974 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1975 - Feb 1975 (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1975 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1975 (Flat-file-folder 5 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1975 (Flat-file-folder 6 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1975 (Flat-file-folder 7 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Sep 1975 (Flat-file-folder 8 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Oct 1975 (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Nov 1975 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 1975 (Box 27, Folder 354)
  - Finished Artwork, Dec 1975 (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 283)
  - Finished Artwork, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 302)
  - Finished Artwork, 1975 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1976 (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Jan 1976 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1976 (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1976 (Box 21, Folder 303)
  - Finished Artwork, Feb 1976 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Finished Artwork, Mar 1976 (Flat-file-folder 6 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Mar 1976 - Sep 1976 (Box 27, Folder 355)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1976 (Flat-file-folder 7 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Apr 1976 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1976 (Flat-file-folder 8 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, May 1976 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Finished Artwork, Jun 1976 (Flat-file-folder 9 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Jul 1976 (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1976 (Box 21, Folder 304)
  - Finished Artwork, Aug 1976 (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)